Google under fire for $45 million deal with Netanyahu's office to spread Gaza genocide
propaganda. They signed this in June 2025. It is time if you were dilly-dallying or if you were
just kind of like, well, you know, I use Google for specific things and so thus I'm not, it's a
It's time to make the switch. It's not feasible to continue to support this. And again, even if you
don't give a damn about Palestine, understand that support of Netanyahu and Israel is support
of the occupation of the United States. It is support of surveillance of you in the United
States. So an option that you can look into is DuckDuckGo. It's an alternative browser that
actually carries over your passwords and your tabs from Chrome. So it just makes it a lot easier to
get into this new space. So listen, this, this is the way, this is the way, this is how we as a people
shift things before we have to physically shift things, which I know y'all ain't ready for anyway.
Now keep in mind, I say this as somebody who is on YouTube because it's so hard to boycott when
there's monopolies, when you have all of these conglomerates that make it impossible to boycott,
which is by design, which is by design. So one of the best options I feel like we can do is at the
very least eradicate them from spaces where there are viable replacements.